<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
 * See the NOTICE file distributed with this work for additional
 * information regarding copyright ownership.
 *
 * This is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify it
 * under the terms of the GNU Lesser General Public License as
 * published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2.1 of
 * the License, or (at your option) any later version.
 *
 * This software is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
 * but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
 * MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU
 * Lesser General Public License for more details.
 *
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU Lesser General Public
 * License along with this software; if not, write to the Free
 * Software Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA
 * 02110-1301 USA, or see the FSF site: http://www.fsf.org.
-->

<xwikidoc version="1.3" reference="ActiveDirectory.Code.Translations" locale="">
  <web>ActiveDirectory.Code</web>
  <name>Translations</name>
  <language/>
  <defaultLanguage>en</defaultLanguage>
  <translation>0</translation>
  <creator>xwiki:XWiki.Admin</creator>
  <creationDate>1476445890000</creationDate>
  <parent>ActiveDirectory.Code.WebHome</parent>
  <author>xwiki:XWiki.Admin</author>
  <contentAuthor>xwiki:XWiki.Admin</contentAuthor>
  <date>1476445962000</date>
  <contentUpdateDate>1476445962000</contentUpdateDate>
  <version>1.1</version>
  <title>Translations</title>
  <comment/>
  <minorEdit>false</minorEdit>
  <syntaxId>plain/1.0</syntaxId>
  <hidden>true</hidden>
  <content>admin.activeDirectory.info=In order to configure and start using Active Directory in XWiki, please make sure that you understand how Windows Active Directory works and how to get data from it. Otherwise, call for help from a system administrator. \nThe configuration is initialized with some default values that work in general. However, small adjustments are needed to be done depending on each server configuration in order to get the right matching.
admin.activeDirectoryConnection=Connection Settings
admin.activeDirectoryConfiguration=Configuration
admin.activeDirectoryConfigurationAdvanced=Advanced
admin.activeDirectoryConfigurationAdvanced.show=Show Advanced Configuration
admin.activeDirectoryConfigurationAdvanced.hide=Hide Advanced Configuration
admin.activeDirectoryMiscellaneous=Miscellaneous
admin.activeDirectoryMiscellaneous.hint=Force to empty the cache containing Active Directory groups.
activeDirectory.error.missingLdapService=Active Directory service is not available. Please verify your installation.
activeDirectory.warning.ldapAuthenticationIsNotEnabled=The system could not connect to Active Directory server because the LDAP authentication service is not enabled. Edit the ##{0}## file, add the following lines and restart the wiki:
activeDirectory.default=(Default)
activeDirectory.aDGroup.placehoder=Active Directory group
activeDirectory.xWikiGroup.placeholder=XWiki group
activeDirectory.aDUserField.placeholder=Active Directory user field
activeDirectory.xWikiUserProperty.placeholder=XWiki user property
activeDirectory.resetGroupCache.submit=Reset group cache
activeDirectory.save.submit=Save
activeDirectory.resetGroupCacheSuccess=Groups cache has been reset.
activeDirectory.newEntry.title=New Entry
activeDirectory.checkConnection=Check connection
activeDirectory.checkConnection.error=Failed to connect to the Active Directory server! Click on this message for details and contact sales@xwiki.com.
activeDirectory.checkConnection.hint=To check the connection for the current setup, the data needs to be saved first. This action will be handle by the "Check connection" button when clicked.
activeDirectory.checkConnection.success=Test connection succeeded!
activeDirecfory.config.initializationComment=Configuration initialized with the default values.

XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap=Enable the Active Directory authentication
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap.hint=Enable the Active Directory authentication for this wiki, otherwise only XWiki authentication will work. If enabled and configured properly, an XWiki user will be created whenever an Active Directory user visits the wiki for the first time.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_server=Active Directory server address
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_server.hint=The address (IP or domain name) of the server to connect to. For example, 127.0.0.1 would be used for a server that is located on the same machine where XWiki is installed.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_port=Active Directory server port
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_port.hint=The port to connect to. For example, 389 would be used if the server is running on the standard LDAP port.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_bind_DN=Active Directory User DN
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_bind_DN.hint=The bind login (user distinguish name) to connect to the server with. This can be left empty for anonymous access to the server. If the server is not configured to accept anonymous access, then the full DN of a user with proper access rights must be provided. For example, cn=admin,dc=example,dc=com is how a user DN should look.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_bind_pass=Active Directory password
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_bind_pass.hint=This can be left empty for anonymous access to the server. This is the password for the previous defined Active Directory User DN and should be used together.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_user_group=Allow Active Directory Authentication only to certain group
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_user_group.hint=This field can be used to provide authentication rights only to the members of an Active Directory group. If this is empty, no restriction will be applied and all the users from the Base DN will be able to authenticate. To configure use the full DN of the group: cn=developers,ou=groups,o=XWiki,c=FR.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_exclude_group=Forbid Active Directory Authentication to certain group
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_exclude_group.hint=This field can be used to deny authentication rights to the members of an Active Directory group. The users that are members of the following group can't authenticate. To configure use the full DN of the group: cn=designers,ou=groups,o=XWiki,c=FR.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_base_DN=Active Directory Base DN
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_base_DN.hint=The Base DN is the root of the tree containing the users and where the server performs the search. E.g. dc=example,dc=com.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_UID_attr=Active Directory UID attribute name
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_UID_attr.hint=Specifies the Active Directory attribute containing the identifier to be used as the XWiki user name. The default is 'sAMAccountName'.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_trylocal=Enable the XWiki authentication
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_trylocal.hint=Enable the XWiki authentication for this wiki, as a fallback solution. Without this setting you will be unable to log into XWiki with local accounts. Also, if Active Directory authentication fails for any reason, the XWiki DB authentication will be tried with the same credentials.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_update_user=Update user from Active Directory after login
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_update_user.hint=If this property is enabled, the XWiki user data will be updated from Active Directory on every login of the user, otherwise the mapping will be done only once, when the user is created.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_update_photo=Update the user photo from Active Directory
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_update_photo.hint=If this property is enabled, the XWiki avatar will be updated from Active Directory on every login of the user, otherwise the photo will not be updated.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_photo_attachment_name=Attachment name used to save the Active Directory photo
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_photo_attachment_name.hint=The Active Directory photo name that will be used in XWiki profile.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_photo_attribute=Active Directory photo attribute name
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_photo_attribute.hint=Specifies the Active Directory attribute that contains the photo image.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_fields_mapping=Active Directory user fields mapping
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_fields_mapping.hint=Set a link between an XWiki user property that needs to store the data from an Active Directory user field. For example, first_name-&gt;givenName (first_name belongs to XWiki.XWikiUsers class and givenName to Active Directory user profile)
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_group_mapping=Active Directory groups mapping
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_group_mapping.hint=Set a link between an XWiki group that needs to store, as members, ther users belonging to an Active Directory group. For example, XWiki.XWikiAdminGroup-&gt;cn=marketing,ou=groups,dc=example. By default, all the users are added into XWiki.XWikiAllGroup.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_groupcache_expiration=Active Directory groups cache expiration
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_groupcache_expiration.hint=Time in seconds after which the list of members in a group is refreshed from Active Directory. The default is 21600 (6 hours).
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_mode_group_sync=When to synchronize the Active Directory groups
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_mode_group_sync.hint=The groups will be synchronized by default on every authentication of a user. For example, if an Active Directory user is moved to a different group, at the next login it will be moved in XWiki in the right group.
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_mode_group_sync_always=At each authentication of a user
XWiki.XWikiPreferences_ldap_mode_group_sync_create=Upon creation of a user

ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl=Enable SSL connection to Active Directory server
ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl.hint=This is an optional configuration. Use it only if the Active Directory server is configured to support LDAP over SSL.
ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl.keystore=Path to SSL keystore
ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl.keystore.hint=Path to the keystore file to use in SSL connection.
ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl.secure_provider=SSL secure provider
ActiveDirectory.Code.ActiveDirectoryConfigClass_ldap_ssl.secure_provider.hint=The java secure provider used in SSL connection. The default is com.sun.net.ssl.internal.ssl.Provider.

## FREE LICENSE
admin.activedirectory=Active Directory
admin.activedirectory.description=Configuration options to authenticate users against an Active Directory server.
activeDirectory.extension.name=Active Directory Application</content>
  <object>
    <name>ActiveDirectory.Code.Translations</name>
    <number>0</number>
    <className>XWiki.TranslationDocumentClass</className>
    <guid>d4b91248-1f4a-4e06-86c0-9c5e8fd42f25</guid>
    <class>
      <name>XWiki.TranslationDocumentClass</name>
      <customClass/>
      <customMapping/>
      <defaultViewSheet/>
      <defaultEditSheet/>
      <defaultWeb/>
      <nameField/>
      <validationScript/>
      <scope>
        <cache>0</cache>
        <disabled>0</disabled>
        <displayType>select</displayType>
        <multiSelect>0</multiSelect>
        <name>scope</name>
        <number>1</number>
        <prettyName>Scope</prettyName>
        <relationalStorage>0</relationalStorage>
        <separator> </separator>
        <separators>|, </separators>
        <size>1</size>
        <unmodifiable>0</unmodifiable>
        <values>GLOBAL|WIKI|USER|ON_DEMAND</values>
        <classType>com.xpn.xwiki.objects.classes.StaticListClass</classType>
      </scope>
    </class>
    <property>
      <scope>WIKI</scope>
    </property>
  </object>
</xwikidoc>
